Guide to the Multicultural Student Services Center records, 1969-2016 RG0056
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Multicultural Student Services Center, 1969-1993; 1980-1993; RG0056 Series 1
  - Monterey Institute of International Studies: Minority Scholarships, 1985-1989; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - National Association for Foreign Student Affairs (NAFSA) Grants, 1989-1991; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Blank Monthly Report Forms, Undated; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - MSSC Job Classification Descriptions, 1977-1988; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    In addition to classification descriptions, this folder also contains a resume, a facilities planning report, and MSSC's misison, objectives, and guidance principles.
  - Completed Monthly Reports, 1985-1990; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - MSSC Educational Opportunity Program, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Student Recommendation Letters, 1988-1992; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    In addition to student recommendation letters, this folder includes resumes and personal statements.
  - Blank Monthly Reports, Undated; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Trio Alumni Awards, Undated; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Remarks by President Trachtenberg Regarding MSSC, 1988-1990; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Blank Phone Logs, Undated; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Telephone Journal Entries, February 1990; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Telecommunications Reports, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - MSSC Staff Telephone Numbers, March 18, 1991; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - GWU Television Video Project, January 1, 1991; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - MSSC Physical Plant Work Requests (Physical Plant Department) [1/2], 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    This folder contains documents that detail alterations made to MSSC's offices and other structural requests.
  - MSSC Physical Plant Work Requests (Physical Plant Department) [2/2], 1990; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program Summer School Request Forms [1/2], 1984-1987; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program Summer School Request Forms [2/2], 1986; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Effective Writing Workshop Materials, March 1987; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program: Five Year University Planning Documents, 1987; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program Student and Staff Emergency Forms, June 19, 1989; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - The STAAR Program: Study Hall Forms, Undated; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Student Admissions Representative Program (STAR), 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Special Projects: Notes on Programs at Other Universities, 1985-1989; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Tony Coates: Spring Fellowship Meeting, April 1990; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Department of English Spring Composition Meeting: Diversity in the Writing Classroom, February 24, 1990; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    General note
    English
  - Establishment of the Multicultural Mathematics and Science Explorers Fund, 1990; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Scholarship Forms and Information, 1989-1992; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Higher Education Research Studies, 1991; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - The Reading Center: Report to the Study Committee, 1990; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Students on Academic Probation, 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - The Standard Operating Procedure for Awarding PREP Monies, 1990; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - PREP 1990 and 1991 Forms and Information, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - 1992 Summer Prep Student Registration, May 16, 1992; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Project Enrich Summer Program, April 29, 1990; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program: Pre-college Review and Enrichment Program [1/2], 1988-1989; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program: Pre-college Review and Enrichment Program [2/2], 1987-1992; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Gail Short Hanson, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program Summer and Fall Housing Applications and Lists, 1989; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - On-Campus Invitation List for PREP Reception, June 1989; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Pre/Post Test Comparisons and SAT Scores for PREP, 1988; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program Executive Summaries, 1988-1990; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - PREP Information and Evaluation Forms, 1991; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Ronald D. F. Palmer, Undated; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - PREP Student Rosters, 1989-1991; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - PREP Course Descriptions, October 6, 1984; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - PREP 1991 Book Receipt and Agreement Forms, August 11, 1991 - August 12, 1991; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - MSSC Payroll Practices Questionnaires, May 4, 1992; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Diversity and Joint Peer Educator Training Materials, 1991-1993; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - PREP Class Schedules and Criteria for Educational Opportunity Grant Recision, 1992; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - PREP Report, 1991; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - PREP Class Schedule, 1992; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - PREP Student Listings, Summer 1992, Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - PREP End of Summer Evaluations, 1992; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - PREP Class Rosters, 1992; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Completed PREP Program Evaluations, 1992; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - PREP Course Syllabus, Undated; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Educational Opportunity Program Graduates, 1969-1981; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Opening Convocation of The George Washington University, September 8, 1989; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program Transfer Students and Mailing List, September 28, 1988; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - The National Society of Black Engineers (NSBE), September 12, 1989; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 67)
    History here...
  - The Educational Opportunity Program Pre/Post Test Roster, Undated; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Christmas Party Supply Forms, Undated; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program Students, FY 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program Staff List, Undated; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Maia Holmes, December 12, 1991; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - List of Addresses, Undated; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 73)
    Fall semester
  - Original Educational Opportunity Program Student List, Undated; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - [Restricted] The Educational Opportunity Program Financial Aid for Incoming Students, 1981-1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program Student Registration Information, 1980-1983; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - High School/College Internship Program (HI/SCIP) Registration, 1978-1985; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - High School/College Internship Program, 1980-1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - High School/College Internship Program Participants, 1979-1985; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Student and Alumni Affairs Divisional Roster, 1981-1983; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Distribution of Housing and Joint Food Board Meal Funds to Educational Opportunity Program Students, 1981-1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Meal Plan Awards for Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) Students, 1980-1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - 1983 University United Way Campaign, July 13, 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Reading Assistance for Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) Students, 1979-1985; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Reading Center and Education 009 Correspondence, 1980-1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Room Requests for the Pre-College Review and Enrichment Program (PREP), 1981-1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence to Bradford Berry, President of the Black Peoples' Union, 1983-1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Lloyd H. Elliott Correspondence, 1977-1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) Summer Program, August 1987; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Professional Development Conference Correspondence and Brochures, 1987-1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) Suspension Lists, 1984-1987; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Pre-College Review and Enrichment Program (PREP) Report, 1989-1990; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Pre-College Review and Enrichment Program (PREP) Program, 1990; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Student Activities Office Correspondence, 1982-1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) Promotional Summary, May 4, 1982; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) Ten Year Report Data, 1979-1980; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program (EOP): A Report on the First Five Years [1/2], 1969-1974; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program (EOP): A Report on the First Five Years [2/2], 1969-1974; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Gail Short Hanson's Correspondence, 1979-1982; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    Related Materials
    Gail Short Hanson was GWU's Dean of Students
  - Marianne R. Phelps's Correspondence, June 9, 1982; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    Marianne R. Phelps was the Assitant within the Provost's for Affirmative Action office.
  - Handbook for The Educational Opportunity Program (EOP), November 1977; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - The Aftermath of Bakke: Should We Use Race in Admissions?, October 6, 1978; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    This paper was presented by William E. Sedlacek at the Council on Legal Educational Opportunities (CLEO) Conference in Washington, D.C. on OCtober 6, 1978.
  - The Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) Day, April 20, 1983; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) Students Attending Dinner/Buffet, June 30, 1982; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program's First Thursday Reception, 1983; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) Publicity Materials, 1976-1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) Annual Report, FY 1981-1982, September 1982; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) Annual Report, FY 1983-1984, July 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program (EOP): A Brief Report of Program Activities, 1984-1985; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) Summary of Highlights, 1984-1985; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) Annual Report, 1985-1986; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) Annual Reports, 1986-1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) Annual Report, 1987-1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) Annual Report, 1988-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) Annual Report, FY 1986-1987, 1985-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence to Students, 1976-1978; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Various Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) Lists of Students, 1972-1983; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Receipt or Service of Legal Actions Against the University, 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Ronald A. Whitmore's Correspondence [1/2], 1981-1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    Ronald A. Whitmore was the Director of the Educational Opportunity Program.
  - Ronald A. Whitmore's Correspondence [2/2], 1983-1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - The National Coalition Building Institute Prejudice Reduction Workshop Model: Trainer's Notes, Undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    Written bty Cherie R. Brown and edited by George J. Mazza.
  - Peer Training Strategies for Welcoming Diversity, Undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    Written by Cherie R. Brown and George J. Mazza.
  - Multicultural Acceptance: A Study of Intergroup Relations, Perceptions, and Experiences Among Randomly Selected Undergraduate Students at the George Washington University, Undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Middle States Self-Study Report, November 29, 1976; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Black People's Union, 1988-1994; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) 20th Year Celebration, February 10, 1990; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) Grant Recision Policy and Criteria, 1986-1991; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Valerie L. Epps Day: A Proclamation by the Mayor of the District of Columbia, March 29, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Valerie L. Epps Day Invitation Lists and Program Materials, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Americans With Disabilities Act at The George Washington University, August 3, 1992; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Janie R. Sylvester's Critique of the Positive Image Program, March 4, 1992; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Janie R. Sylvester was the Executive Assitant of Off-Campus Program at GWU. She was specifically critiquing the "Color Analysis" segment of the Positive Image Program.
  - Janet Lopez, Museum Education Program Applicant, May 1992; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - 1991-92 Judicial Report Correspondence, August 26, 1992; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Black Business Association Correspondence, May 7, 1992; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Guide to Campus Life Brochure Correspondence, August 26, 1992; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - International Black Betterment Organization Correspondence, Undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - CCAS 001 Evaluations, 1991-1992; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - The George Washington University Art Gallery Exhibitions, 1991-1993; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - 1992 Excellence in Student Life Awards, February 25, 1992; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - "I Have a Dream" Program Correspondence, September - October 1991; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Meeting with Reverend Lauren Smith Correspondence, January 31, 1992; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    Reverend Lauren Smith was the Ecumenical Campus Minister and Chair of the Board of Chaplains.
  - Toni E. Jackson, Office Skills Instructor Application, Undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Complaint: Professor Daniel Kane's Spring 91 BAd 201 Class, December 1991; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Total Quality Management (TQM) Correspondence, October 24, 1991; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - The Faculty Senate Meeting Agenda, September 30, 1991; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - The Lifestyle Diversity of the United States: An Enrollment Feasibility Briefing, October 1991; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - The Reporting Requirements of the Cafritz Foundation, October 30, 1990; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - GW & DC High Schools: A Hometown Connection (The 21st Century DC Scholars Program, The Educational Opportunity Program), Undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Ping Wong's Resume, Undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Institutionalizing Multiculturalism: A Successful Program Model, February 1, 1991; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Security Observation Report, October 28, 1991; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on General Literacy Requirements, October 24, 1991; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Faculty Senate Committee Meeting Correspondence, October 24, 1991; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - For Immediate Release: GW Awards its First Pre-Doctoral Fellowships, October 22, 1991; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Final Report, Arts Partners Planning Grant, October 23, 1991; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Board of Trustees Student Affairs Committee Meeting, October 11, 1991; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - International Services Office Budget Projection Report for Fiscal years 1990-1991 and 1991-1992, 1990-1992; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - First Thursday Coffee Hour, January 12, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Participation with Fairfax County Public Schools in the College and University Partnership Program, May 24, 2019; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - University Counseling Center Proposal: Comprehensive Alcohol and Drug Education Program, September 28, 1990; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Minority Faculty Recruiting Efforts at Sinclair Community College Correspondence, April 20, 1990; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence Regarding the Needs of Students of Color on the GW Campus, April 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Access to Student Information Systems (SIS) Information, August 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - GW Campus/Community Interaction Memorandum, March 8, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Health Behaviors of College Students Questionnaire, January 31, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Tuition Rates for 1989-90 Memorandum, January 19, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - The Ralph Bunche Institute Fellowship Program for Minority Student PhD Candidates at CUNY, January 3, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - General Correspondence to Valerie L. Epps, 1988-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Prejudice Reduction Workshop, January 6, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Pennsylvania Black Conference on Higher Education, December 1, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Adelaide McGuinn Cromwell, Black People's Union Honored Guest, Undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Proposed Addition to University Hazing Policy Memorandum, January 6, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Survey for Emergency Work Reception Customer Service, November 23, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Resident Assistant Application Correspondence, January 19, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - One Percent Reductions in 1988-89 Base Budges Correspondence, January 19, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Workshops for the University Archives and Records Management Program Correspondence, December 20, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - First Annual Student Leaders Conference (ASC) Correspondence, October 24, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - HI/SCIP, January 3, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - National Science Foundation-sponsored Study of Equity and Excellence in Higher Education Correspondence, September 26, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Center for Learning and Leading Correspondence, December 15, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) Holiday Pot Luck Dinner, December 15, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - University of Minnesota Law School Correspondence to Valerie L. Epps, November 29, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Career Services Center's Career Week '89 Career Resource Room Correspondence, November 15, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Telecommunications Services Office Correspondence, November 28, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Status of Linda L. Wing Correspondence, September 6, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Orientation Week Highlights Memorandum, August 17, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Membership Survey of the American College Personnel Association's Committee on Multicultural Affairs, June 10, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Transitional Year Programme, University of Toronto Correspondence, November 1, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Polytechnic of North London and GWU Correspondence, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Howard University Black History Month Forum Planning Correspondence, October 19, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Jerome Scott, 1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Beyond the Dream: A Celebration of Black History, October 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. National Day of Remembrance, October 27, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Budget Up-date! (1988-89), October 25, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - President Stephen Joel Trachenberg's Congratulations for Valerie L. Epps, October 13, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - A Workshop on Meeting Management Memorandum, October 24, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Kaplan LSAT Program, Fall 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Her Majesty's Inspectorate Team (H.M.I.) Study of U.S. Post Secondary Education, October 10-20, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. Convocation Program Subcommittee Members Scheduling Correspondence, October 10, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) Statistics, September 28, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Roger A. Mayorga Position Action Request, May 6, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Committee on the Martin Luther King, Jr. Convocation: "Correction of a Previous Memo.", October 7, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - The GWU Committee on Racial Awareness, September 15, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - The GWU Speech and Hearing Clinic Correspondence, September 7, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - 11th Annual Congressional Black Caucus (CBC)/ Black Women's Agenda, Inc. (BWA) Workshop and Luncheon Invitation, September 16, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Black Student Leadership Conference Brochure, October 28, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Request for Information on Contract Negotiations and Printed Materials for Staff Meeting, August 31, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Gayle Y. Phillips Resume, August 24, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Letter from the Office of the Deputy Superintendent to Valerie L. Epps, August 11, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - 1988-89 Budgets Correspondence, August 4, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Leadership Seminars for the Educational Opportunity Program (EOP), April 11, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Jo Ann Johnson, Prospective Minority Student Correspondence, April 11, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Correspondence Thanking Valerie L. Epps for her Assistance, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Brief Summary of 1987-88 Recruitment Activities, July 18, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Proposal to Establish "The Eugene F. Ford Scholarships", Undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 92)
    This proposal discusses expanding GWU's Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) to Prince Geroge's County residents through the establishment of "The Eugene F. Ford Scholarships."
  - Annotated Version of the PREP List from the Office of Student Financial Aid, June 26, 1987; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - A Special GWU/Washington Post Program for Students at Eastern High School, November 12, 1987; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - Fall Resident Assistant Training Workshop, July 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - Contributions for Bill Smith's Retirement Gift, August 15, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 96)